<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
  <content contentuid="had0cdb3ag3c97g4e69gaa6fgf0b629b94236" version="1">&lt;i&gt;Disregard all sense of decorum or reverence. Grab the sword with both hands and PULL.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h991b8e06g9539g4505g8f5egca8275edce23" version="1">*No matter how you grip or tug, the sword remains firmly lodged in the stone. You grip the blade for better leverage, but only end up cutting yourself. The blood drips onto the sword.*</content>
  <content contentuid="he5603bb7gd11eg4d2fga57dg1f33592f029c" version="1">*Surprisingly, the blade flickers and glows. The blade slides out with barely any force from your hands.*</content>
  <content contentuid="hc6f06331g7414g4a7dg8144gdfbbee6be5a9" version="1">*A feeling of hundreds of spiders crawling down your spine is your only brief warning that something is terribly, terribly wrong.*</content>
  <content contentuid="ha87046eegb699g4623gb5adga1c1c936f733" version="1">*Your bones start to creak and contort. Your vision turns black, and immeasureable pain grips you. You can feel your organs &lt;i&gt;shifting&lt;/i&gt; as your body grows.*</content>
  <content contentuid="hb8074486g8eefg4ad0g91d8g382b345cf8f8" version="1">*New limbs and appendages creep out of your abdomen. Your body's center of mass changes, adjusting to your new body's legs and weight.*</content>
  <content contentuid="h73d4e285g2e02g4f69g87ceg910fcac43c7b" version="1">*It's an odd sensation - not only feeling the sensations of each individual leg, but being able to control them as well.*</content>
  <content contentuid="h9f02d733g7babg4d28gb8cfg6acc79e0eb77" version="1">*As the pain subsides, and the transformation nears its end, the only thought on your mind is how Lloth has violated your body. It is &lt;i&gt;hers&lt;/i&gt; now. This thing you've become - it is you now. Forever.*</content>
  <content contentuid="h2ed6cb1ag47b6g448dga525gf26f4f7fc6ed" version="1">Mod_Lloth_Drider DEBUG</content>
  <content contentuid="h488e5d37g04f1g4e12gaf40g0622a0f99123" version="1">Transform, or unTransform.</content>
  <content contentuid="h61b11b2ag6897g4311g8340gf742e7dfc1c4" version="1">Transformation</content>
  <content contentuid="hc3a51b65gbe80g4f19g9038g9311d6a99873" version="1">Transform into drider.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc3fe4e84g13c7g4921g8dc2gb0275bd45e15" version="1">Untransformation</content>
  <content contentuid="h4f87a7e6g5824g444cgb861gea0d11b36674" version="1">Remove all shapeshifts/transformations.</content>

</contentList>